catholictv.org 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | CatholicTV

## Privacy Policy: Boston Catholic Television Center Inc. a.k.a The CatholicTV Network, iCatholic (Media), Your Catholic Broadband Network, CatholicTV

### 1\. Protecting your privacy

 Your information is in no way shared with third parties for marketing purposes. (i.e., no tracking devices) Your account information is password-protected. CatholicTV does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If CatholicTV learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, CatholicTV will remove that post. CatholicTV, or people who post on CatholicTV, may provide links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for, nor can in any way control, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of every website visited.

### 2\. Data we collect

 Your name, address, phone number and email address is requested for purposes such as, but not limited to, providing subscription services, registering complaints, commendations or feedback on programming, soliciting for advertising by CatholicTV, updates for new events, etc. CatholicTV does not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. We may collect personal information if you provide comments or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on CatholicTV's forums (e.g., [www.iCatholic.com](http://www.icatholic.com/)) or pages that you do not intend to make public. Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, device and browser used, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the CatholicTV site, and to otherwise provide our service to you.

### 3\. Data we store

 Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. Although the information is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

### 4\. Archiving and display of CatholicTV postings by search engines and other sites

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with CatholicTV – including, but not limited to [archive.org](http://www.archive.org/index.php), google.com, and groups.yahoo.com – will archive or otherwise make available CatholicTV postings.

### 5\. Interaction With Children Online

CatholicTV is committed to the protection of children’s online privacy. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) governs information gathered online from or about children under the age of 13. Verifiable consent from a child’s parent or guardian is required before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from a child under age 13. If a CatholicTV website intends to collect information about children under 13 years old, COPPA-required information and instructions will be provided by the specific web page that collects information about the child. The web page will specify exactly what the information will be used for, who will see it, and how long it will be kept.

### 6\. Circumstances in which CatholicTV may release information

 CatholicTV may disclose user information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to follow the legal process or in response to requests from law enforcement.

### 7\. International Users

Due to the international dimension of CatholicTV, the data provided by the user may be utilized for the purposes identified in this policy, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

### 8\. Feedback

We appreciate your feedback! Please [let us know](http://www.catholictv.org/contact-us) if you have any questions or concerns.
